[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vodka is traditional for this country. People there like to flavor vodka with lemon peel, pepper or herbs.", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["Ukraine", "Macedonia", "Romania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1992 black-and-white movie, written and directed by Woody Allen, stars Madonna as a tightrope artist?", "correct_answer": "Shadows and Fog", "incorrect_answers": ["Play It Again, Sam", "Another Woman", "Manhattan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is telesophobia?", "correct_answer": "Fear of being last", "incorrect_answers": ["Fear of religious ceremonies", "Fear of being ignored", "Fear of being first"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All US Presidents have worn glasses.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Until what century was alchemy considered a serious science in Europe?", "correct_answer": "16th century", "incorrect_answers": ["14th century", "13th century", "18th  century"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What biblical number is emphasized and repeated in the 2003 comedy Bruce Almighty?", "correct_answer": "Seven", "incorrect_answers": ["Forty", "Twelve", "Three"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which U.S. state is nicknamed The Cowboy State?", "correct_answer": "Wyoming", "incorrect_answers": ["Texas", "Iowa", "Idaho"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of lunch meat did Allison fling onto the statue in The Breakfast Club, before making her Capn Crunch and pixy stick sandwich?", "correct_answer": "pimiento loaf", "incorrect_answers": ["bologna", "ham", "salami"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the national flower of Wales?", "correct_answer": "Daffodil", "incorrect_answers": ["Daisy", "Rose", "Posy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actor who played Jules neighbor Ron in St. Elmos Fire also played David Silvers dad on Beverly Hills 90210.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term is used to denote a trained and knowledgeable wine professional?", "correct_answer": "sommelier", "incorrect_answers": ["cuvee", "salmanazar", "negociant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of cheese is the Roquefort, also called Rochefort?", "correct_answer": "Blue cheese", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow cheese", "Pink cheese", "Creamy cheese"]}]